Hello.
We are Cumminses.
Today is the first time that we are going out as members of Cumminses.
I would like to observe Asakusa while wearing a kimono that makes my neck look beautiful
I would like to observe Asakusa.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm very honored to be here.
There must be some kind of festival going on today!
Let's go!
It's good!
Here we go.
Amen to that.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm glad.
You haven't eaten anything today.
I've been eating a little too much chow.
Yeah, I know.
Pink.
I'm pink.
My hair is like this.
Purple.
I green
The growth
A cat or something
Obi is cute
Black is rare.
It's so mature.
Her hair is also very nice.
They're showing each other their kimonos.
Where's Iroha's kimono?
I'm wearing...
A little green today.
- Nice! It's so unexpected! Really?
I put pink here.
The psyllium colors are pink and yellowish green.
- It's just perfect! It's so nice!
- What about you, Nao? What about you, Nao?
I added a little pink and purple.
So cute! I had the flowers made a little bigger too.
There's a tasting corner.
Oh, my God! I want some!
Let's taste it when we get up there!
We're tasting.
What was that?
The one with the rice cakes.
Bon appétit.
Taste the rice cakes.
Bon appétit!
Yum! Nice and salty!
Delicious!
I'd love to have this at a family gathering. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
There's a sweet potato shop. I love this place.
Is it good?
Oh, my God!
- It's so good! It's so good! Strawberry strawberries!
We have strawberries!
We have strawberries everywhere!
- Let's eat! Let's eat!
- Corps commander, first! Bon appétit!
- Yum!
- Yum! Yummy?
- What flavor? What's that?
- It's some kind of vegan soft serve ice cream.
- Oh, my God! What is that?
- It's kind of light and healthy.
- What's vegan?
- What's vegan? It looks delicious!
- It's so thin!
What? Why?
Because it's vegan?
Is it different?
Yes! Right?
No milk.
It tastes so good!
Mmm! It's sweet!
Yeah, it's good!
It's delicious.
Mmm!
Mmm! Yum! Yum!
It's good. Here we go.
Show him later.
He's so cute.
Looks delicious.
Yum!
Oh, no!
Hurry up with this one, too!
Oh no, it's a cross section!
Cross-section
Yum!
Well, here we are at Hanayashiki!
Yay!
Here at Hanayashiki...
There's a man here in Hanayashiki who's a member of Kubin Sesu.
I just wanted to say hello to him.
Let's go meet him... together.
Who is it?
Take a guess.
Let's go!
I want to go on that one.
Can you do the screams?
I think I can do that one.
That one.
We don't have to wait too long for that one.
What's your point of view?
I'm just excited about today.
You've done your research?
I've done a lot of research.
I'm glad you did.
Is this it?
Could it work?
It might work.
I think it'll work.
Is this going to work?
It's okay. It's the senior game.
Of course it is.
You don't need to know.
I'm off.
Okay, I'm just gonna wave to the guys.
Can I wave?
Be brave.
Wow!
Surprisingly fast. Surprisingly fast.
Oh, my heart!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
Whoa!
Come on!
Oh, no.
Centrifugal force
Oh no!
You know what?
Vibrations are bad.
I don't mean that part.
That's what's scary.
Oh, my God.
It was so much easier.
I thought I was gonna fall.
Centrifugal force, all the way down.
Oh, thank you.
I've got fans coming up to me.
“We're rooting for you.
I'm so glad you're doing this.
Well, goodbye, Sweden.
Oh, my gosh.
It's really nice today, isn't it?
It's great.
And what's the road we're on now?
Why do you think we're so... chief there?
You're really great! You're really great! I said, “It's too long!
Who are you?
It's so nice!
Oh, it's on, it's on!
The wind feels good.
You look like a big sister today.
She's black.
A pinch of the pole.
You're right.
It's out of my hands.
It's out of my control
Mother, mother
Please bear with me
please bear with me
Cute
Something, you know, here
I get along with everyone
It's nice.
Wait, our time together is over.
I don't want to say goodbye.
You're all I've got.
No, no, no, no.
I want to go home.
I'm not leaving.
What?
Welcome home.
I'm back.
How'd it go?
It was the perfect time.
When I was a little girl, it felt so much bigger.
But the world looks different now.
What? Target shooting?
Let's try shooting!
Go for it. Go for it.
What are we going for?
What should we go for?
Prank toilets?
Let's go!
It's a roundabout!
300 meters.
I hit it!
But even if I hit it, we're still going up!
Then next time, or not, I'll go to the colorful mother who has it and will do it
I'm thinking of going to a beach chick, but it's too far away!
Good luck!
That sounded really good, didn't it?
It sounded so good
Nice try!
That was close.
This is a tough one.
Here we go.
I'm in the middle of something amazing.
I'm sure they'll tell you.
Our Ayame.
I'm going for the chick.
Yay!
Just the middle one.
So cute!
Yay!
Placing.
Ohhhh!
Oh, my gosh!
A chick to remember you by.
How was it?
It was so much fun!
We all had a blast wearing kimonos.
When I looked at it again...
You all have such beautiful necks.
It's more ayamehon.
Restraint.
I wish we had more time.
I'd love to go back there again, but this time I'm going to nominate each and every one of you.
I'm going to nominate you.
I've been talking about it for a long time and I've really just been talking about it. I feel very comfortable with her, she's very calm, I can tell she's very sensitive.
Oh, it's nice... to be able to take care of yourself.
Like Cherry Blossom.
How's it going? Does it look okay?
It's very comfortable.
That's good.
Sakura's probably a very thoughtful person.
I just wish we could be on her side and let her in.
I'm glad.
That's why I wanted you to join us.
I've seen how hard you've been working.
So now we get a song from the corps.
I think it'll give me more opportunities to show her dance moves and sexy expressions.
I thought it would be a great opportunity for me to share her dance moves and sexy expressions with everyone.
That's why I was so happy that she joined the corps.
I was so surprised when they called my name.
I was really happy.
Really?
I didn't think I'd ever be a part of something like this.
Not at all.
I was so happy.
Mao...
You've been in touch lately.
It comes at a time when I'm really anxious.
That's why I'm so relieved.
I want to say thank you, too.
You're so kind, Maomon. I know you have a lot of things you don't like to say.
I'm sure there are many things you have to endure.
I know you have to put up with a lot
But just here...
I want you to know that no matter what happens, I'm on your side.
It feels so good. I'm so happy.
You're so kind, I want to cry.
Really?
I'll tell you a good story.
I'll cry.
Beautiful tears.
I'm about to cry over nothing.
I'm really glad I met you.
I'm glad I met you.
You're breaking up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you.
It doesn't break up.
I'm so happy.
That's great!
So I went to the haunted house, which was my original purpose.
We're here to see a certain someone... who's a rock star...
booboo we are members of KUBINSESS because of our distinctive necks, but we wanted to say hello to the original 66 members of KUBINSESS, so we're going to split into two groups and go in.
Boo-boo!
I can hear you so well!
Aren't you scared at last?
Sakura?
Where's the front? Where's the front?
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
What?
Stop it!
What's out there? What's out there?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey, Mr. Kubi, where are you?
Did we miss something?
Look out, look out, look out!
Watch out!
Is that Mr. Kubi?
Oh, this is him!
May I say hello?
I'm the leader of the Stace. I'm Miki. Nice to meet you.
I'm the leader of the “Legion.” Nice to meet you.
Coronavirus.
What? Where?
You're fired.
Where did you go?
We didn't see Mr. Kubi.
Mr. Kubi?
You're not coming?
He's here!
Oh, no!
It's coming!
Are you gonna answer it?
No, it's not coming out.
Oh, my God.
I met him, and he said something about me being a big talker.
I said it, didn't I?
I didn't get to meet him properly, so I thought I'd leave it to you guys.
To be honest, I was really intimidated.
That's scary.
Leave it to me!
Hey, wait up!
Hey, this could be ours.
Yeah, it could be ours.
They look like such great kids.
Ayumi's first time in a haunted house.
I'm off! I'll go say hi! Go say hi! I'll go say hi! I asked you to...
What should I do? Wait! I'm scared!
Wait! I really don't think I can do it...
I really don't think I can do it... Let's ban that running.
I won't be able to keep up.
Wait, I can't.
What? Still going?
No, you're still going.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, wait.
DITO, DITO, DITO.
Oh, that's not fair.
DITO DITO DITO DITO DITO DITO
Ah, I don't care
Oh, it's too much trouble
Uh, do what you want, I'll leave it to you.
It's about to go bang.
Don't bang me, please.
Let's just be prepared.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't look at me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Here you go.
Oh, yeah.
I'm taking a lot of pictures.
You don't hear much shouting, do you?
I don't see 66B.
You mean there's no 66B?
It's so dark, so dark.
What, what, what, what?
What the hell?
I heard footsteps.
Footsteps are the scariest things I've ever heard.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is this it?
Senpai.
We're...
Kumminses.
Pleased to meet you.
Worst.
Wait.
Ayami is too strong!
Ayami-you're so in love with her!
Oh, here she comes.
Oh, here it comes.
It's so cool!
I'm a little surprised.
Thank you for saying hello to her... and for avenging her death for us.
But he was so quiet, wasn't he?
I'm glad you had a good day.
I'm glad you liked it.
I'll see you later.